He's losing their minds
Man with the Screaming Brain is a comedy, horror, science
fiction film directed by Bruce Campbell.
The brains of a Russian taxi driver and a wealthy businessman are
brought together in one body by a mad scientist.
William Cole, played by Bruce Campbell.
Tatoya, played by Tamara Gorski.
Pavel, played by Ted Raimi.
Jackie, played by Antoinette Byron.
Dr. Ivan Ivanovich Ivanov, played by Stacy Keach.
Yegor, played by Vladimir Kolev.
Man with the Screaming Brain is a 2005 science fiction/slapstick film
co-written, produced, and directed by Bruce Campbell, who also stars.
It is Campbell's feature film directorial debut.
The film was co-written by David Goodman and co-stars Ted Raimi.
The film centers on William Cole, a wealthy American executive who travels to Bulgaria with his wife, only for
their marriage and lives to unravel after she begins an affair with their taxi driver, Yegor.
A violent encounter with a vengeful maid leaves William and Yegor dead, but William is revived
through a brain transplant that forces him to share his body with Yegor's consciousness.
The film explores themes of operation, taxi driver,
comic book, face operation, bulgaria.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.